let questions = [
    {
        "answer": "Namibia",
        "options": [
            "Namibia",
            "Niger",
            "Chad",
            "Ghana"
        ],
        "question": "Windhoek is the capital of__________?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "Euro",
        "options": [
            "Zolty",
            "Peso",
            "Euro",
            "Escudo"
        ],
        "question": "The currency of portugal is__________?",
    },
    {
        "answer": "Almaty",
        "options": [
            "Astana",
            "Almaty",
            "Baku",
            "Tashkent"
        ],
        "question": "Which of the following city served as capital of Kazakhstan till 1997?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "North Atlantic Ocean",
        "options": [
            "North Atlantic Ocean",
            "South Atlantic Ocean",
            "Pacific Ocean",
            "Arabian Sea"
        ],
        "question": "Bermuda Triangle is located in__________?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "Ramon Magsaysay Award",
        "options": [
            "Ramon Magsaysay Award",
            "Booker Prize",
            "Pulitzer Prize",
            "None of them"
        ],
        "question": "Which among the following is known as Asia a version of “Noble prize”?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "Geneva",
        "options": [
            "London",
            "Geneva",
            "Rome",
            "Paris"
        ],
        "question": "The headquarter of EFTA is in_____________?",

    },
    {
        "answer": "China",
        "options": [
            "Japan",
            "China",
            "South Koera",
            "None of These"
        ],
        "question": "Which country Built A 250-Acre Solar Farm Shaped Like A Giant Panda:",

    },
    {
        "answer": "White Bellbird",
        "options": [
            "Macaws",
            "Cockatoos",
            "White Bellbird",
            "None of these"
        ],
        "question": "________ is the World’s Loudest Bird",


    },
    {
        "answer": "Feb 29",
        "options": [
            "Feb 29",
            "Feb 28",
            "March 01",
            "Feb 01"
        ],
        "question": "_______ is known as leap day or leap year day",

    },
    {
        "answer": "China",
        "options": [
            "Japan",
            "Russia",
            "China",
            "None of These"
        ],
        "question": "Where is the World’s longest sea bridge ?",
        

    }
]



// let questions = [
//     {
//         "answer": "Namibia",
//         "options": [
//             "Namibia",
//             "Niger",
//             "Chad",
//             "Ghana"
//         ],
//         "question": "Windhoek is the capital of__________?",
//         "userAnswer": "Niger",
//         "score": 0
//     },
//     {
//         "answer": "Euro",
//         "options": [
//             "Zolty",
//             "Peso",
//             "Euro",
//             "Escudo"
//         ],
//         "question": "The currency of portugal is__________?",
//         "userAnswer": "Euro",
//         "score": 1
//     },
//     {
//         "answer": "Almaty",
//         "options": [
//             "Astana",
//             "Almaty",
//             "Baku",
//             "Tashkent"
//         ],
//         "question": "Which of the following city served as capital of Kazakhstan till 1997?",
//         "userAnswer": "Almaty",
//         "score": 1
//     },
//     {
//         "answer": "North Atlantic Ocean",
//         "options": [
//             "North Atlantic Ocean",
//             "South Atlantic Ocean",
//             "Pacific Ocean",
//             "Arabian Sea"
//         ],
//         "question": "Bermuda Triangle is located in__________?",
//         "userAnswer": "Pacific Ocean",
//         "score": 0
//     },
//     {
//         "answer": "Ramon Magsaysay Award",
//         "options": [
//             "Ramon Magsaysay Award",
//             "Booker Prize",
//             "Pulitzer Prize",
//             "None of them"
//         ],
//         "question": "Which among the following is known as Asia a version of “Noble prize”?",
//         "userAnswer": "Ramon Magsaysay Award",
//         "score": 1
//     },
//     {
//         "answer": "Geneva",
//         "options": [
//             "London",
//             "Geneva",
//             "Rome",
//             "Paris"
//         ],
//         "question": "The headquarter of EFTA is in_____________?",
//         "userAnswer": "Geneva",
//         "score": 1
//     },
//     {
//         "answer": "China",
//         "options": [
//             "Japan",
//             "China",
//             "South Koera",
//             "None of These"
//         ],
//         "question": "Which country Built A 250-Acre Solar Farm Shaped Like A Giant Panda:",
//         "userAnswer": "China",
//         "score": 1
//     },
//     {
//         "answer": "White Bellbird",
//         "options": [
//             "Macaws",
//             "Cockatoos",
//             "White Bellbird",
//             "None of these"
//         ],
//         "question": "________ is the World’s Loudest Bird",
//         "userAnswer": "White Bellbird",
//         "score": 1
//     },
//     {
//         "answer": "Feb 29",
//         "options": [
//             "Feb 29",
//             "Feb 28",
//             "March 01",
//             "Feb 01"
//         ],
//         "question": "_______ is known as leap day or leap year day",
//         "userAnswer": "Feb 29",
//         "score": 1
//     },
//     {
//         "answer": "China",
//         "options": [
//             "Japan",
//             "Russia",
//             "China",
//             "None of These"
//         ],
//         "question": "Where is the World’s longest sea bridge ?",
//         "userAnswer": "China",
//         "score": 1
//     }
// ]




















export default questions 